<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<odoo>
    <template id="about_page_template" name="About Page">
        <t name="About Page" t-name="sps_theme.about_page">
            <t t-name="website.about">
                <t t-call="website.layout">
                    <div id="wrap" class="oe_structure oe_empty">
                        <section>
                            <div class="container">
                                <div class="text-center pt32 pb32">
                                    <h1 class="about-header"> About SPS Surgical </h1>
                                </div>
                                <div class="section-description pb32">
                                    <div class="row">
                                        <div class="col-md-9 m-auto">
                                            <div class="video-section-wrapper mt-0">
                                                <div class="video-wrapper">
                                                    <iframe width="100%" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/P10W72mLfGM?rel=0" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture" allowfullscreen=""></iframe>
                                                </div>
                                            </div>
                                            <h2 class="section-title ml0">We Provide High-Quality, Cost-Saving Surgical Solutions.</h2>
                                            <p>
                                               SPS is a leader in providing cost-saving solutions for healthcare facilities across the United States who choose to save money without sacrificing quality of care.
                                                    We accomplish this by <span> presenting hospitals and surgery centers with two ways to save </span> on their high-volume surgical disposables.
                                            </p>
                                            <div class="story-list">
                                                <div class="bulleted-list">
                                                    <div>1</div></div>
                                                <div class="list-description">
                                                    <p><span>SPS provides a liquidation solution for surgical disposables</span> when they become non-moving and are no longer being used by the facility. This can be due to product conversions, contract changes, or physician departures. We purchase these surgical disposables that would otherwise remain un-used and eventually expire on the shelves of the OR, injecting cash directly into the hospital’s budget.</p>
                                                </div>
                                            </div>
                                            <div class="story-list pt-2">
                                                <div class="bulleted-list">
                                                    <div>2</div></div>
                                                <div class="list-description">
                                                    <p><span>SPS acts as an independent distributor</span> of un-used, in date surgical disposables. We sell the same high-volume products that your facility is currently buying from vendors, at an even greater discount than top tier pricing. We also provide the flexibility to purchase individual items in "eaches," rather than in cases, which helps in the unique case of a preferential product that is outside your normal buying patterns (Physician Preference Item)—and avoids disrupting any contract compliances.</p>
                                                </div>
                                            </div>
                                        </div>
                                    </div>
                                </div>
                            </div>
                        </section>
                    </div>
                    <section class="our-mission padding-60-y">
                        <div class="container">
                            <p class ="pt-0">
                                OUR MISSION is to bring revenue back to hospitals for
                                their surplus, un-used surgical products, while offering
                                them discounts on high-volume products they are
                                currently utilizing.
                            </p>
                        </div>
                    </section>
                    <div class="seprator"><div class="red"></div><div class="black"></div></div>
                    <section class="help-section padding-100-y">
                        <div class="container">
                            <div class="banner-wrapper">
                                <img src="/sps_theme/static/src/images/help.jpg" class="img-fluid"/>
                            </div>
                            <h3 class="section-title text-center">HOW WE HELP</h3>
                            <div class="row">
                                <div class="col-md-8 text-left m-auto">
                                    <p>We have successfully eliminated hundreds of thousands of dollars from our customer’s costs by buying and selling the surgical surplus they would have otherwise thrown away.</p>
                                </div>
                            </div>
                            <div class="row pt-5">
                                <div class="col-md-4 mb-3">
                                    <div class="help-box">
                                        <p class="box-title">WE PROVIDE PERSONALIZED SERVICE AT EVERY LEVEL</p>
                                        <p class="box-content">
                                            We cater our solution to serve
                                            the entire spectrum of healthcare
                                            facilities-from large health systems
                                            to small surgical centers. At each
                                            level, our services are personalized
                                            to fit our customers’ needs.
                                        </p>
                                    </div>
                                </div>
                                <div class="col-md-4  mb-3">
                                    <div class="help-box">
                                        <p class="box-title">WE HELP YOU SAVE MONEY WITHOUT SACRIFICING QUALITY</p>
                                        <p class="box-content">
                                            Our business model allows our customers to save money, without interrupting surgeon preferences or hospital contracts. We accomplish this by providing hospitals, not one, but two cost-savings solutions for their high-volume surgical disposables.
                                        </p>
                                    </div>
                                </div>
                                <div class="col-md-4 mb-3">
                                      <div class="help-box">
                                          <p class="box-title">WE INCREASE EFFICIENCY AND REDUCE WASTE</p>
                                          <p class="box-content">
                                                Our service keeps valuable medical
                                                devices from expiring on the shelf and
                                                turning into waste; allowing hospitals
                                                to redirect resources towards
                                                increasing their quality of care.
                                          </p>
                                      </div>
                                </div>
                            </div>
                        </div>
                    </section>
                </t>
            </t>
        </t>
    </template>
</odoo>