<odoo>
    <template id="policy_template" name="Terms">
        <t t-name="website.terms">
            <t t-call="website.layout">
                <div id="wrap" class="oe_structure oe_empty"/>
                <section class="about-us-section">
                    <div class="container">
                        <div class="text-center pt32 pb32">
                            <h1  class="about-header"> Privacy Policy </h1>
                          </div>
                        <div class="row">
                            <div class="col-md-12 mb32">
                                <div class="about-us-description">
                                    <div class="subtitle text-center">
                                        <span class="s1">SURGICAL PRODUCT SOLUTIONS LLC</span>
                                    </div>
                                    <div class="subtitle-light text-center" >
                                        <span class="s2">STANDARD Terms and Conditions OF SALE</span>
                                    </div>
                                    <div class="subtitle text-center">
                                        <span class="s1">Last Updated October 12, 2018
                                        </span>
                                    </div>
                                    <div class="section-description mt-5">
                                        <ol class="ol1">
                                            <li class="li2">
                                                    <span class="s3">APPLICABILITY.</span>
                                                <ol class="ol2">
                                                    <li class="li2">
                                                        <p class="s1">These Standard Terms and Conditions of Sale (these
                                                            "<span>Terms</span>") are the only terms which govern the sale of the
                                                            goods (the "<span>Goods</span>") by Surgical Product Solutions LLC
                                                            ("<span>Seller</span>") to the buyer ("<span>Buyer</span>") named on the
                                                            accompanying invoice and/or sales confirmation (each, a "<span>
                                                                Sales Confirmation</span>"). Notwithstanding anything herein to
                                                            the contrary, if a written contract signed by both parties is in
                                                            existence covering the sale of the Goods covered hereby, the
                                                            terms and conditions of said contract shall prevail to the
                                                            extent they are inconsistent with these Terms.
                                                        </p>
                                                    </li>
                                                    <li class="li2">
                                                        <p class="s1">The applicable Sales Confirmation and these Terms
                                                            (collectively, this "<span>Agreement</span>") comprise the entire
                                                            agreement between the parties, and supersede all prior or
                                                            contemporaneous understandings, agreements, negotiations,
                                                            representations and warranties, and communications, both written
                                                            and oral. These Terms prevail over any of Buyer's general terms
                                                            and conditions of purchase. Fulfillment of Buyer's order does
                                                            not constitute acceptance of any of Buyer's terms and conditions
                                                            and does not serve to modify or amend these Terms.
                                                        </p>
                                                    </li>
                                                </ol>
                                            </li>
                                            <li class="li2">
                                                <span class="s3">DELIVERY.</span>
                                                <ol class="ol2">
                                                    <li class="li2">
                                                        <p class="s1">The goods will be delivered within a reasonable
                                                            time after the receipt of Buyer's purchase order, subject to
                                                            availability of the Goods. Seller shall not be liable for any
                                                            delays, loss or damage in transit.
                                                        </p>
                                                    </li>
                                                    <li class="li2">
                                                        <p class="s1">Seller may, in its sole discretion, without
                                                            liability or penalty, make partial shipments of Goods to Buyer.
                                                            Each shipment will constitute a separate sale, and Buyer shall
                                                            pay for the units shipped whether such shipment is in whole or
                                                            partial fulfillment of Buyer's purchase order.
                                                        </p>
                                                    </li>
                                                </ol>
                                            </li>
                                            <li class="li2">
                                                <span class="s3">QUANTITY.</span>
                                                <p class="s1">
                                                    If Seller delivers to Buyer a quantity of Goods of up to 5% more or less than the quantity set
                                                    forth in the Sales Confirmation (or at least 75% of the quantity set
                                                    forth in the Sales Confirmation if the undelivered Goods are on back
                                                    order), Buyer shall not be entitled to object to or reject the Goods or
                                                    any portion of them by reason of the surplus or shortfall and shall pay
                                                    for such Goods the price set forth in the Sales Confirmation adjusted
                                                    pro rata.
                                                </p>
                                            </li>
                                            <li class="li2">
                                                    <span class="s3">SHIPPING TERMS</span>
                                                <p class="s1">
                                                    <span>AND RISK OF LOSS. </span>
                                                     Delivery shall be made, and risk of loss shall pass to Buyer, FOB
                                                    Seller’s place of business.
                                                </p>
                                            </li>
                                            <li class="li2">
                                                <span class="s3">AMENDMENT AND MODIFICATION.</span>
                                                <p class="s1">
                                                    These Terms may only be
                                                    amended or modified in a writing which specifically states that it
                                                    amends these Terms and is signed by an authorized representative of each
                                                    party.
                                                </p>
                                            </li>
                                            <li class="li2">
                                                    <span class="s3">PRICE.</span>
                                                <p class="s1">
                                                   Buyer shall purchase
                                                    the Goods from Seller at the price (the "<b>Price</b>") set forth in the
                                                    Sales Confirmation. All Prices are exclusive of all sales, use and
                                                    excise taxes, and any other similar taxes, duties and charges of any
                                                    kind imposed by any governmental authority on any amounts payable by
                                                    Buyer. Buyer shall be responsible for all such charges, costs and taxes;
                                                    provided that, Buyer shall not be responsible for any taxes imposed on,
                                                    or with respect to, Seller's income, revenues, gross receipts, personnel
                                                    or real or personal property or other assets.
                                                </p>
                                            </li>
                                            <li class="li2">
                                                    <span class="s3">PAYMENT TERMS.</span>
                                                <ol class="ol2">
                                                    <li class="li2">
                                                        <p class="s1">If Buyer is an approved customer, Buyer shall pay
                                                            all invoiced amounts due to Seller within 30 days from the date
                                                            of Seller's invoice unless otherwise stated in the Sales
                                                            Confirmation. If Buyer is not an approved customer, Buyer shall
                                                            make payment of all invoiced amounts due to Seller prior to
                                                            shipment of the Goods by Seller. If Buyer is
                                                            an international customer, all payments hereunder shall be made
                                                            by wire transfer or paypal transfer.
                                                        </p>
                                                    </li>
                                                    <li class="li2">
                                                        <p class="s1">Buyer shall pay interest on all late payments at
                                                            the lesser of the rate of 1.5% per month or the highest rate
                                                            permissible under applicable law, calculated daily and
                                                            compounded monthly. Buyer shall reimburse Seller for all costs
                                                            incurred in collecting any late payments, including, without
                                                            limitation, attorneys' fees. In addition to all other remedies
                                                            available under these Terms or at law (which Seller does not
                                                            waive by the exercise of any rights hereunder), Seller shall be
                                                            entitled to suspend the delivery of any Goods if Buyer fails to
                                                            pay any amounts when due hereunder and such failure continues
                                                            for ten (10) days following written notice thereof.
                                                        </p>
                                                    </li>
                                                    <li class="li2">
                                                        <p class="s1">Buyer shall not withhold payment of any amounts due
                                                            and payable by reason of any set-off of any claim or dispute
                                                            with Seller, whether relating to Seller's breach, bankruptcy or
                                                            otherwise.
                                                        </p>
                                                    </li>
                                                </ol>
                                            </li>
                                            <li class="li2">
                                                <span class="s3">LIMITED WARRANTY.</span>
                                                <ol class="ol2">
                                                    <li class="li3">
                                                        <p class="s1">Seller warrants to Buyer that the Goods will
                                                            conform to Seller’s Quality Assurance &amp; Service Guarantee,
                                                            available at <a
                                                                    href="http://www.surgicalproductsolutions.com/docs/SPS-Quality-Assurance.pdf">
                                                                http://www.surgicalproductsolutions.com/docs/SPS-Quality-Assurance.pdf
                                                            </a> and incorporated herein by reference, for a period
                                                            beginning on the date of shipment and expiring on the earlier of
                                                            (i) one (1) year from the date of shipment of the Goods and (ii)
                                                            the expiration date of the applicable Good (the "<span>Warranty
                                                                Period</span>").&amp;nbsp;
                                                        </p>
                                                    </li>
                                                    <li class="li2">
                                                        <p class="s1">The Goods consist of products manufactured by a
                                                            third party ("<span>Third Party Product</span>"). For the avoidance of
                                                            doubt,
                                                            <span>EXCEPT FOR THE WARRANTY SET FORTH IN SECTION 8(a), SELLER
                                                                MAKES NO REPRESENTATIONS OR WARRANTIES WITH RESPECT TO ANY
                                                                THIRD PARTY PRODUCT, INCLUDING ANY (a) WARRANTY OF
                                                                MERCHANTABILITY; (b) WARRANTY OF FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR
                                                                PURPOSE; (c) WARRANTY OF TITLE; OR (d) WARRANTY AGAINST
                                                                INFRINGEMENT OF INTELLECTUAL PROPERTY RIGHTS OF A THIRD
                                                                PARTY, WHETHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED BY LAW, COURSE OF DEALING,
                                                                COURSE OF PERFORMANCE, USAGE OF TRADE OR OTHERWISE.
                                                            </span>
                                                            Notwithstanding the foregoing, upon request, Seller shall use
                                                            its commercially reasonable efforts to pass through to Buyer any
                                                            manufacturer, distributor, or other third party warranties
                                                            covering such Third Party Products included in the Goods and in
                                                            favor of Seller.
                                                        </p>
                                                    </li>
                                                    <li class="li2">
                                                        <p class="s1">With respect to any such Goods being in breach of
                                                            the limited warranty set forth in Section 8(a) hereof during the
                                                            Warranty Period, Seller shall, in its sole discretion, either:
                                                            (i) repair or replace such Goods (or the defective part) or (ii)
                                                            credit or refund the price of such Goods at the pro rata
                                                            contract rate; provided that, if Seller so requests, Buyer
                                                            shall, at Seller's expense, return such Goods to Seller.
                                                        </p>
                                                    </li>
                                                    <li class="li2">
                                                        <p class="s1">
                                                            <span>THE REMEDIES SET FORTH IN SECTION 8(c) SHALL BE BUYER'S SOLE
                                                                AND EXCLUSIVE REMEDY AND SELLER'S ENTIRE LIABILITY FOR ANY
                                                                BREACH OF THE LIMITED WARRANTY SET FORTH IN SECTION 8(a).&amp;nbsp;
                                                            </span>
                                                        </p>
                                                    </li>
                                                </ol>
                                            </li>
                                            <li class="li2">
                                                <span class="s3">LIMITATION OF LIABILITY.</span>
                                                <ol class="ol2" style="list-style-type: lower-alpha;">
                                                    <li class="li2">
                                                        <p class="s1">
                                                            <span>IN NO EVENT SHALL SELLER BE LIABLE TO BUYER OR ANY THIRD
                                                                PARTY FOR ANY LOSS OF USE, REVENUE OR PROFIT, OR FOR ANY
                                                                CONSEQUENTIAL, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, EXEMPLARY, OR
                                                                PUNITIVE DAMAGES WHETHER ARISING OUT OF BREACH OF CONTRACT,
                                                                TORT (INCLUDING NEGLIGENCE) OR OTHERWISE, REGARDLESS OF
                                                                WHETHER SUCH DAMAGES WERE FORESEEABLE AND WHETHER OR NOT
                                                                SELLER HAS BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES,
                                                                AND NOTWITHSTANDING THE FAILURE OF ANY AGREED OR OTHER
                                                                REMEDY OF ITS ESSENTIAL PURPOSE.
                                                            </span>
                                                        </p>
                                                    </li>
                                                    <li class="li2">
                                                        <p class="s1">
                                                            <span>IN NO EVENT SHALL SELLER'S AGGREGATE LIABILITY ARISING OUT OF
                                                                OR RELATED TO THIS AGREEMENT, WHETHER ARISING OUT OF OR
                                                                RELATED TO BREACH OF CONTRACT, TORT (INCLUDING NEGLIGENCE)
                                                                OR OTHERWISE, EXCEED THE TOTAL OF THE AMOUNTS PAID TO SELLER
                                                                FOR THE GOODS SOLD HEREUNDER.
                                                            </span>
                                                        </p>
                                                    </li>
                                                    <li class="li2">
                                                        <p class="s1">The limitation of liability set forth in Section
                                                            9(b) above shall not apply to liability resulting from Seller's
                                                            gross negligence or willful misconduct.
                                                        </p>
                                                    </li>
                                                </ol>
                                            </li>
                                            <li class="li2">
                                                <span class="s3">COMPLIANCE WITH LAW.</span>
                                                <p class="s1">
                                                    Buyer shall comply with all applicable laws, regulations and ordinances.
                                                    Buyer shall maintain in effect all the licenses, permissions,
                                                    authorizations, consents and permits that it needs to carry out its
                                                    obligations under this Agreement.
                                                </p>
                                            </li>
                                            <li class="li2">
                                                <span class="s3">TERMINATION.</span>
                                                <p class="s1">
                                                    In addition to any
                                                    remedies that may be provided under these Terms, Seller may terminate
                                                    this Agreement with immediate effect upon written notice to Buyer, if
                                                    Buyer: (i) fails to pay any amount when due under this Agreement and
                                                    such failure continues for ten (10) days after Buyer's receipt of
                                                    written notice of nonpayment; (ii) has not otherwise performed or
                                                    complied with any of these Terms, in whole or in part; or (iii) becomes
                                                    insolvent, files a petition for bankruptcy or commences or has commenced
                                                    against it proceedings relating to bankruptcy, receivership,
                                                    reorganization or assignment for the benefit of creditors.
                                                </p>
                                            </li>
                                            <li class="li2">
                                                <span class="s3">WAIVER.</span>
                                                <p class="s1">
                                                    No waiver by Seller of
                                                    any of the provisions of this Agreement is effective unless explicitly
                                                    set forth in writing and signed by Seller. No failure to exercise, or
                                                    delay in exercising, any right, remedy, power or privilege arising from
                                                    this Agreement operates, or may be construed, as a waiver thereof. No
                                                    single or partial exercise of any right, remedy, power or privilege
                                                    hereunder precludes any other or further exercise thereof or the
                                                    exercise of any other right, remedy, power or privilege.
                                                </p>
                                            </li>
                                            <li class="li2">
                                                <span class="s3">CONFIDENTIAL INFORMATION.</span>
                                                <p class="s1">
                                                    All non-public,
                                                    confidential or proprietary information of Seller, including but not
                                                    limited to documents, data, business operations, customer lists,
                                                    pricing, discounts or rebates, disclosed by Seller to Buyer, whether
                                                    disclosed orally or disclosed or accessed in written, electronic or
                                                    other form or media, and whether or not marked, designated or otherwise
                                                    identified as "confidential" in connection with this Agreement is
                                                    confidential, solely for the use of performing this Agreement, and may
                                                    not be disclosed or copied unless authorized in advance by Seller in
                                                    writing. Seller shall be entitled to injunctive relief for any violation
                                                    of this Section. This Section does not apply to information that is: (a)
                                                    in the public domain; (b) known to Buyer at the time of disclosure; or
                                                    (c) rightfully obtained by Buyer on a non-confidential basis from a
                                                    third party.
                                                </p>
                                            </li>
                                            <li class="li2">
                                                <span class="s3">FORCE MAJEURE.</span>
                                                <p class="s1">
                                                    The Seller shall not be
                                                    liable or responsible to Buyer, nor be deemed to have defaulted or
                                                    breached this Agreement, for any failure or delay in fulfilling or
                                                    performing any term of this Agreement when and to the extent such
                                                    failure or delay is caused by or results from acts or circumstances
                                                    beyond the reasonable control of Seller including, without limitation,
                                                    acts of God, flood, fire, earthquake, explosion, governmental actions,
                                                    war, invasion or hostilities (whether war is declared or not), terrorist
                                                    threats or acts, riot, or other civil unrest, national emergency,
                                                    revolution, insurrection, epidemic, lockouts, strikes or other labor
                                                    disputes (whether or not relating to either party's workforce), or
                                                    restraints or delays affecting carriers or inability or delay in
                                                    obtaining supplies of adequate or suitable materials, materials or
                                                    telecommunication breakdown or power outage.
                                                </p>
                                            </li>
                                            <li class="li2">
                                                <span class="s3">RELATIONSHIP OF THE PARTIES.</span>
                                                <p class="s1">
                                                    The relationship
                                                    between the parties is that of independent contractors. Nothing
                                                    contained in this Agreement shall be construed as creating any agency,
                                                    partnership, joint venture or other form of joint enterprise, employment
                                                    or fiduciary relationship between the parties, and neither party shall
                                                    have authority to contract for or bind the other party in any manner
                                                    whatsoever.
                                                </p>
                                            </li>
                                            <li class="li2">
                                                <span class="s3">NO THIRD-PARTY BENEFICIARIES.</span>
                                                <p class="s1">
                                                    This Agreement is for
                                                    the sole benefit of the parties hereto and their respective successors
                                                    and permitted assigns and nothing herein, express or implied, is
                                                    intended to or shall confer upon any other person or entity any legal or
                                                    equitable right, benefit or remedy of any nature whatsoever under or by
                                                    reason of these Terms.
                                                </p>
                                            </li>
                                            <li class="li2">
                                                <span class="s3">GOVERNING LAW.</span>
                                                <p class="s1">
                                                    All matters arising out
                                                    of or relating to this Agreement is governed by and construed in
                                                    accordance with the internal laws of the Commonwealth of Pennsylvania
                                                    without giving effect to any choice or conflict of law provision or rule
                                                    (whether of the Commonwealth of Pennsylvania or any other jurisdiction)
                                                    that would cause the application of the laws of any jurisdiction other
                                                    than those of the Commonwealth of Pennsylvania.
                                                </p>
                                            </li>
                                            <li class="li2">
                                                <span class="s3">SUBMISSION TO JURISDICTION.</span>
                                                <p class="s1">
                                                    Any legal suit, action or proceeding arising out of or relating to this Agreement shall be
                                                    instituted in the federal courts of the United States of America or the
                                                    courts of the Commonwealth of Pennsylvania in each case located in the
                                                    City of Pittsburgh and County of Allegheny, and each party irrevocably
                                                    submits to the exclusive jurisdiction of such courts in any such suit,
                                                    action or proceeding.
                                                </p>
                                            </li>
                                            <li class="li2">
                                                <span class="s3">NOTICES.</span>
                                                <p class="s1">
                                                    All notices, request,
                                                    consents, claims, demands, waivers and other communications hereunder
                                                    (each, a "<span>Notice</span>") shall be in writing and addressed to the
                                                    parties at the addresses set forth on the face of the Sales Confirmation
                                                    or to such other address that may be designated by the receiving party
                                                    in writing. All Notices shall be delivered by personal delivery,
                                                    nationally recognized overnight courier (with all fees pre-paid),
                                                    facsimile (with confirmation of transmission) or certified or registered
                                                    mail (in each case, return receipt requested, postage prepaid). Except
                                                    as otherwise provided in this Agreement, a Notice is effective only (a)
                                                    upon receipt of the receiving party, and (b) if the party giving the
                                                    Notice has complied with the requirements of this Section.
                                                </p>
                                            </li>
                                            <li class="li2">
                                                <span class="s3">SEVERABILITY.</span>
                                                <p class="s1">
                                                    If any term or
                                                    provision of this Agreement is invalid, illegal or unenforceable in any
                                                    jurisdiction, such invalidity, illegality or unenforceability shall not
                                                    affect any other term or provision of this Agreement or invalidate or
                                                    render unenforceable such term or provision in any other jurisdiction.
                                                </p>
                                            </li>
                                            <li class="li2">
                                                <span class="s3">SURVIVAL.</span>
                                                <p class="s1">

                                                    Provisions of these Terms which by their nature should apply beyond
                                                    their terms will remain in force after any termination or expiration of
                                                    this Agreement including, but not limited to, the following provisions:
                                                    Compliance with Laws, Confidential Information Governing Law, Submission
                                                    to Jurisdiction, and Survival.
                                                </p>
                                            </li>
                                        </ol>
                                    </div>
                                </div>
                            </div>
                        </div>
                    </div>
                </section>
            </t>
        </t>
    </template>
</odoo>