<odoo>
    <template id="about_page" name="About Page">
        <t t-name="website.about">
            <t t-call="website.layout">
                <div id="wrap" class="oe_structure oe_empty"/>
                <section class="about-us-section">
                    <div class="container">
                        <div class="row">
                            <div class="col-md-12 col-sm-12">
                                <div class="header-title">
                                    <h1>About</h1>
                                </div>
                                <div class="about-us-description">
                                    <p>SPS is a leader in providing cost-saving solutions for
                                        healthcare facilities across the United States who choose
                                        to save money without sacrificing quality of care. We accomplish
                                        this by providing hospitals and surgery centers two ways to save
                                        on their high-volume surgical disposables. We help our customers
                                        recover significant budget costs by purchasing their un-used,
                                        in-date surgical surplus while at the same time, providing them
                                        additional cost savings and flexibility when purchasing the same
                                        high volume products they are currently utilizing.
                                    </p>
                                </div>
                            </div>
                        </div>
                    </div>
                </section>
                <section class="service-section">
                    <div class="container">
                        <hr/>
                        <div class="row">
                            <div class="col-md-4 col-sm-4">
                                <div class="service-picture">
                                    <img alt="warehouse SPS Shop" class="img-responsive"
                                         src="/website_cstm/static/src/img/warehouse-woman-ABOUT.jpg"/>
                                </div>
                            </div>
                            <div class="col-md-8 col-sm-8">
                                <div class="service-picture-description">
                                    <p>SPS provides a solution for surgical disposables when they become
                                        jeopardized and are no longer being used by the facility.
                                        This can be due to product conversions, contract changes,
                                        or physician departures. We purchase these surgical disposables
                                        that would otherwise remain un-used and eventually expire on the
                                        shelves of the OR, injecting cash directly into the hospital’s budget.
                                    </p>
                                </div>
                            </div>
                        </div>
                        <hr/>
                        <div class="row">
                            <div class="col-md-8  col-sm-8">
                                <div class="service-picture-description">
                                    <p>SPS acts as an independent distributor of un-used, in date surgical disposables.
                                        We can sell your facility high volume products that you are currently buying
                                        from top vendors,
                                        at an even greater discount from top tier pricing. We also provide the
                                        flexibility to purchase individual items in “eaches,” rather than in cases,
                                        which helps in the unique case of a preferential product that is outside your
                                        normal buying patterns
                                        (Physician Preference Item)—and avoids disrupting any contract compliances.
                                    </p>
                                </div>
                            </div>
                            <div class="col-md-4  col-sm-4">
                                <div class="service-picture">
                                    <img alt="warehouse SPS Shop" class="img-responsive" src="/website_cstm/static/src/img/Scissors-ABOUT.jpg"/>
                                </div>
                            </div>
                        </div>

                    </div>
                </section>
            </t>
        </t>
    </template>
</odoo>