<odoo>
    <template id="faqs_page" name="Faqs Page">
        <t t-name="website.faqs">
            <t t-call="website.layout">
                <div id="wrap" class="oe_structure oe_empty"/>
                <section class="about-us-section">
                    <div class="container">
                        <div class="row">
                            <div class="col-md-12 mb32">
                                <div class="header-title">
                                    <h1>FAQs</h1>
                                </div>
                                <div class="about-us-description">
                                    <p>
                                        <strong>How do I place an order?</strong>
                                    </p>
                                    <p> Simply browse through our inventory and add any items to your shopping cart and hit "checkout".
                                        You will then be given a total including shipping charges. You may then pay using a credit card, PayPal,
                                        or Purchase Order number if you are an approved customer.</p>
                                    <p>
                                        <strong>Where does your supply come from?</strong>
                                    </p>
                                    <p>At SPS, we typically purchase this product from hospitals and
                                        large health systems that undergo conversions, trials, physician
                                        departures and contract changes where they find a remaining balance of
                                        unused, in-date surplus product. We purchase products from licensed facilities
                                        within the United States with legitimate title ownership of the merchandise who
                                        can confirm that safety, storage, and distribution procedures are being properly enforced.</p>
                                    <p>
                                        <strong>Do you sell expired or reprocessed / re-sterilized items?</strong>
                                    </p>
                                    <p>No, SPS does not sell items that are expired, however SPS does work with
                                        reprocessed or re-sterilized items. Reprocessed items are indicated with "-RP"
                                        added to the end of the product reference number.  Re-sterilized items are indicated
                                        with "-R".  We mostly work with in-date and unused surgical disposables that are in
                                        the original manufactures packaging.  Our expiration dates range from 6 months to 3+
                                        years.  For some reason a product has less than 6 months in expiration, you will
                                        be notified immediately by an SPS representative.</p>
                                    <p>
                                        <strong>How soon will my order ship?</strong>
                                    </p>
                                    <p>All FedEx Ground orders placed by 4:30pm EST are processed and
                                        shipped the same day.  The cut-off time for FedEx Express orders is 3:30pm EST.
                                        All orders after 4:30PM Eastern Standard Time will be shipped next day unless noted.
                                        SPS is not responsible for delays in shipping due to orders arriving after 4:30PM
                                        Eastern Standard Time.</p>
                                    <p>
                                        <strong>What are your shipping methods?</strong>
                                    </p>
                                    <p>All orders are shipped FedEx ground unless expedited shipment is requested.
                                        FedEx Ground shipments are 2-5 day delivery.</p>
                                    <p>
                                        <strong>What are the shipping and handling costs?</strong>
                                    </p>
                                    <p>Shipping and handling costs are based on the items
                                        purchased and range from $7.00 to $10.00 for standard ground
                                        shipping with in the United States. Overnight shipping charges are dependent on your location and size/weight of the items.</p>
                                    <p>For items shipping outside the United States, costs will vary
                                        depending on your location.  If you are outside the United States &amp;amp;
                                        would like a shipping quote, you can contact us directly.</p>
                                    <p>
                                        <strong>Do you ship outside the United States?</strong>
                                    </p>
                                    <p>Yes, we ship our products worldwide.  Shipping charges are
                                        calculated at checkout or you can contact us for a shipping quote.</p>
                                    <p>
                                        <strong>What are your payment methods?</strong>
                                    </p>
                                    <p>We accept Visa, MasterCard, American Express &amp;amp; Discover
                                        either online or over the phone. PayPal is accepted as well.
                                        Purchase orders are also accepted from approved customers only.
                                        If you would like to set up an account to be invoiced, please call us today.</p>
                                    <p>
                                        <strong>Is there a minimum order amount?</strong>
                                    </p>
                                    <p>There are no minimum order requirements.
                                        The quantities listed next to each item are what
                                        we currently have available for purchase as our website is real-time.</p>
                                    <p>
                                        <strong>Can I save my shipping and billing information so that I do not need to enter it every time?</strong>
                                    </p>
                                    <p>Yes.  You can register by clicking the "Create an account"
                                        link located at the top of the home page.</p>
                                    <p>
                                        <strong>Do you offer any guarantee on your products?</strong>
                                    </p>
                                    <p>Customers are allowed to return items upon request,
                                        including ordering errors. Any customer not satisfied with
                                        any device upon receipt will have that device replaced at no
                                        charge if within 15 days of order placement. Furthermore,
                                        if that specific product is not available, SPS will give the customer equal
                                        dollar credit towards any other device(s) in inventory.
                                        Should any products sold reach its expiration date prior to receipt of that product,
                                        SPS will replace the product at no charge and if that
                                        specific product is not available,
                                        equal dollar credit towards any other device(s) in inventory will be issued. </p>
                                    <p>
                                        <strong>Do I need to have a medical license to purchase from your website?</strong>
                                    </p>
                                    <p>Yes, you should be a licensed medical professional to purchase any of our items.</p>
                                    <p>
                                        <strong>How do I retrieve my login information?</strong>
                                    </p>
                                    <p>If you forgot your password, you can click the "forgot your password"
                                        link in the Log-in section to have it emailed to you.
                                        If you do not remember your user name or did not register an email,
                                        give us a call and we will be happy to look it up for you.</p>
                                </div>
                            </div>
                        </div>
                    </div>
                </section>
            </t>
        </t>
    </template>
</odoo>