<odoo>
    <template id="terms_of_purchase" name="Terms Of Purchase">
        <t t-name="website.terms_of_purchase">
            <t t-call="website.layout">
                <div id="wrap" class="oe_structure oe_empty"/>
                <section class="about-us-section">
                    <div class="container">
                        <div class="row">
                            <div class="col-md-12 mb32">
                                <div class="header-title">
                                    <h1>Terms Of Purchase</h1>
                                </div>
                                <div class="about-us-description">

                                    <div class="p1" style="text-align: center;">
                                        <span class="s1">
                                            <b>SURGICAL PRODUCT SOLUTIONS LLC</b>
                                        </span>
                                    </div>
                                    <div class="p1" style="text-align: center;">
                                        <span class="s2">STANDARD TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF PURCHASE</span>
                                    </div>
                                    <div class="p1" style="text-align: center;">
                                        <span class="s1">
                                            <b>Last Updated October 12, 2018</b>
                                        </span>
                                    </div>
                                    &amp;nbsp;
                                    <ol class="ol1">
                                        <li class="li2">
                                            <strong>
                                                <span class="s3">AGREEMENT.</span>
                                            </strong>
                                            <span class="s1">
                                             <!--   <strong>.</strong> &amp;nbsp;-->
                                                <span class="Apple-converted-space">&amp;nbsp;</span>These Standard Terms and Conditions of Purchase
                                                (“<b>Terms and Conditions</b>”) along with any purchase orders or purchase offers (each, a “<b>Purchase Order</b>”),
                                                any releases, requisitions, work orders, shipping instructions, supplemental terms and conditions and
                                                any other document of Surgical Product Solutions LLC, a Pennsylvania limited liability company (“Buyer”),
                                                including without limitation Buyer’s Quality Assurance &amp; Service Guarantee available at
                                                http://www.surgicalproductsolutions.com/docs/SPS-Quality-Assurance.pdf and incorporated herein by reference,
                                                whether expressed in written form or by electronic data interchange provided by Buyer (collectively,
                                                the “<b>Agreement</b>”), will exclusively govern the purchase of goods by Buyer and represents the entire agreement
                                                between Buyer and the vendor set forth in the applicable Purchase Order (including such vendor's agents or suppliers,
                                                “<b>Seller</b>”) with respect thereto. Acceptance of Buyer’s purchase order shall constitute Seller’s agreement to comply
                                                with and be bound by the Agreement, including but not limited to these Terms and Conditions.
                                            </span>
                                        </li>
                                        <li class="li2">
                                            <strong>
                                                <span class="s3">ACCEPTANCE OF PURCHASE ORDERS.</span>
                                            </strong>
                                            <span class="s1">
                                               <!-- <strong>.</strong> &amp;nbsp;-->
                                               <span class="Apple-converted-space">&amp;nbsp;</span>Buyer's commitment to
                                                purchase goods from Seller arises only upon Buyer's
                                                issuance of a Purchase Order to Seller and Seller’s acceptance or deemed
                                                acceptance of such Purchase Order.  Any forecasts, commitments,
                                                projections, representations about quantities to be purchased or other
                                                estimates provided to Seller are for planning purposes only and shall
                                                not be binding upon Buyer, and Buyer shall not be liable for any amounts
                                                incurred by Seller in reliance on such estimates.  Acknowledgement of a
                                                Purchase Order by any means, including without limitation, by supply of
                                                the goods called for by a Purchase Order, shall be deemed acceptance of
                                                such Purchase Order.  The terms set forth in a Purchase Order take
                                                precedence over any alternative terms in any other document connected
                                                with the applicable transaction except in the case of a direct conflict
                                                with these Terms and Conditions, in which case these Terms and Conditions
                                                shall prevail unless the parties have expressly and specifically agreed
                                                in writing that the conflicting Purchase Order terms are intended to
                                                override these Terms and Conditions in the event of a conflict.
                                                A Purchase Order shall not constitute an acceptance by Buyer of any
                                                offer to sell, any quotation, or any proposal by Seller.  Reference in a
                                                Purchase Order to any such offer to sell, quotation or proposal shall in
                                                no way constitute a modification of any of the terms of the Agreement or
                                                such Purchase Order. <b>ANY ATTEMPTED CONFIRMATION OR ACKNOWLEDGMENT BY
                                                SELLER THAT CONTAINS TERMS INCONSISTENT WITH OR IN ADDITION TO THE TERMS
                                                OF THE APPLICABLE PURCHASE ORDER OR BUYER'S TERMS AND CONDITIONS IS NOT
                                                BINDING UNLESS SPECIFICALLY ACCEPTED BY BUYER IN WRITING.  THE AGREEMENT
                                                EXPRESSLY LIMITS ACCEPTANCE TO THE TERMS OF THE APPLICABLE PURCHASE ORDER
                                                AND BUYER'S TERMS AND CONDITIONS, AND BUYER HEREBY OBJECTS TO AND REJECTS
                                                ANY DIFFERENT OR ADDITIONAL TERMS CONTAINED IN ANY RESPONSE TO ANY OF ITS
                                                PURCHASE ORDERS.  EACH PURCHASE ORDER EXPRESSLY INCLUDES ALL IMPLIED WARRANTIES
                                                AND ALL OF BUYER’S REMEDIES SET FORTH IN THE UNIFORM COMMERCIAL CODE.
                                                EXCEPT AS STATED ABOVE, THE TERMS OF THE AGREEMENT ARE THE SOLE AND
                                                EXCLUSIVE TERMS ON WHICH BUYER AGREES TO BE BOUND.</b>
                                            </span>
                                        </li>
                                        <li class="li2">
                                            <strong>
                                                <span class="s3">PRICES AND PAYMENTS.</span>
                                            </strong>
                                            <span class="s1">
                                               <!-- <strong>.</strong>-->
                                            </span>
                                            <ol class="ol2" style="list-style-type: lower-alpha;">
                                                <li class="li2">
                                                    <span class="s1">Buyer shall pay all invoices in accordance with the
                                                        payment terms set forth in the applicable Purchase Order. Unless
                                                        the face of such Purchase Order states to the contrary, all prices
                                                        are (a) firm and not subject to increase or additional charges;
                                                        (b) in U.S. dollars; and (c) inclusive of all duty and taxes other
                                                        than sales or use taxes Seller is required by law to collect from Buyer.
                                                        Such sales or use taxes shall not be included in Seller’s invoice
                                                        if Buyer indicates that the goods are exempt from such taxes.
                                                        Applicable taxes shall be separately stated on Seller’s invoice.
                                                        Seller warrants the pricing for any goods or services shall not
                                                        exceed the pricing for the same or comparable goods offered by
                                                        Seller to third parties.  Seller shall promptly inform Buyer of
                                                        any lower pricing levels for same or comparable goods or services,
                                                        and the parties shall promptly make the appropriate price adjustment.
                                                    </span>
                                                </li>
                                                <li class="li2">
                                                    <span class="s1">Unless otherwise stated on the face of a Purchase Order,
                                                        payment terms are due net thirty (30) days from the later of the
                                                        required date identified on such Purchase Order, the received date
                                                        of the goods in Buyer’s receiving system or the date of receipt
                                                        of valid invoice by Buyer.  Buyer shall be entitled to reject
                                                        Seller’s invoice if it fails to include Buyer’s applicable Purchase
                                                        Order number or is otherwise inaccurate, and any resulting delay
                                                        in payment shall be Seller’s responsibility.  No extra charges of
                                                        any kind will be allowed unless specifically agreed in writing by Buyer.
                                                        Buyer reserves the right to deduct from any amount due Seller for
                                                        any goods ordered any amount Seller owes Buyer with respect to
                                                        any claims of any nature whatsoever in favor of Buyer against
                                                        Seller, whether or not related to the applicable Purchase Order
                                                        and whether now existing or hereafter arising.  Buyer reserves
                                                        the right to withhold any payments due Seller, without penalty
                                                        or forfeiture, until all disputes (whether or not related to a
                                                        Purchase Order and whether or not existing or arising in the future)
                                                        between Buyer and Seller, are settled. Any assignee of Seller’s
                                                        rights to payment hereunder shall be subject to Buyer’s rights under this paragraph.
                                                    </span>
                                                </li>
                                            </ol>
                                        </li>
                                        <li class="li2">
                                            <strong>
                                                <span class="s3">WARRANTIES.</span>
                                            </strong>
                                            <span class="s1">Seller covenants, represents and warrants to Buyer, in addition
                                                to all warranties expressed or implied at law, that all goods supplied by
                                                Seller and the use, design, construction, assembly, production, shipment,
                                                sale, packaging, labeling, packing, advertising, instructions and warnings
                                                or lack thereof and other printed matter furnished or authorized by Seller,
                                                shall (a) be un-used (except for such goods which are clearly described on
                                                the face of the Purchase Order to be used) and of merchantable quality, free
                                                from defects in design, workmanship and/or materials, including, without
                                                limitation, such defects as could create a risk of injury or damage to persons
                                                or property; (b) be fit and suitable for their intended end use; (c) not
                                                violate or breach any agreement that Seller may have with any other person
                                                or entity, including any other manufacturer, distributor or end user; (d)
                                                conform to all specifications and other descriptions set forth or incorporated
                                                in each Purchase Order; (e) be properly stamped, tagged, labeled, or marked
                                                with such information as may be required by any applicable law, regulation
                                                or order or by Buyer; (f) be within any expiration date indicated on the
                                                packaging of the goods; (g) have been stored under proper conditions to
                                                preserve the quality of the goods; (h) meet all applicable requirements
                                                of all applicable United States federal, state and local laws and regulations;
                                                (i) have clear title, free of all liens and encumbrances; and (j) be free of
                                                claims of third parties of any nature whatsoever arising out of or related to
                                                the goods or the Purchase Order. Seller also covenants to use commercially
                                                reasonable efforts to pass-through, or arrange for assignment of, any
                                                representations and warranties applicable to the goods covered by the
                                                applicable Purchase Order and made to Seller by any manufacturer, distributor
                                                or other third-party with respect to such goods. Seller’s representations and
                                                warranties herein shall survive the delivery, inspection and acceptance of
                                                goods to or by Buyer and any resale of goods by Buyer, and any attempt by
                                                Seller to limit, disclaim or restrict any such warranties or remedies by
                                                acknowledgment or otherwise shall be null, void and ineffective.  The above
                                                warranties shall apply for twenty-four (24) months from delivery of goods,
                                                or such longer period of time as customarily provided by Seller or as provided
                                                under the Uniform Commercial Code, as extended for delays such as those due to
                                                non-conforming goods and services.  The warranties shall apply to Buyer, its
                                                successors, assigns and the end users of goods and services covered by each
                                                Purchase Order.  If any of the goods are found to be defective or otherwise not
                                                in conformity with the warranties in this Section during the warranty period,
                                                then, Buyer, in addition to any other rights, remedies and choices it may have
                                                by law, contract or at equity, and in addition to seeking recovery of any and
                                                all damages and costs emanating therefrom, at its option and sole discretion
                                                and at Seller’s expense may: (a) require Seller to replace nonconforming goods
                                                with goods and/or services that conform to all requirements of the applicable
                                                Purchase Order; (b) take such actions as may be required to cure all defects
                                                and/or bring the goods into conformity with all requirements of the applicable
                                                Purchase Order, in which event all related costs and expenses (including, but
                                                not limited to, material, labor and handling costs) and other reasonable
                                                charges shall be for Seller's account; and/or (c) reject and return all or
                                                any portion of such goods.  Any repaired or replaced goods shall carry
                                                warranties on the same terms as set forth above, with the warranty period
                                                being the greater of the original unexpired warranty or twenty-four (24)
                                                months after repair or replacement.
                                            </span>
                                        </li>
                                        <li class="li2">
                                            <strong>
                                                <span class="s3">CHANGES.</span>
                                            </strong>
                                            <span class="s1">
                                                <!--<strong>.</strong>-->
                                                <span class="Apple-converted-space">&amp;nbsp;</span>Buyer may at any time
                                                make changes in written, electronic or facsimile form to any Purchase Order,
                                                including changes in the quantity, delivery time or place, methods of shipment,
                                                warranties, packing, or time or place of delivery at any time.  Any Seller claim
                                                for adjustment will be deemed waived unless asserted within ten (10) days from
                                                Seller’s receipt of the change or suspension notification, and may only include
                                                reasonable, direct costs that will necessarily be incurred as a direct result
                                                of the change.
                                            </span>
                                        </li>
                                        <li class="li2">
                                            <strong>
                                                <span class="s3">COMPLIANCE WITH LAWS.</span>
                                            </strong>
                                            <span class="s1">
                                               <!-- <strong>.</strong>-->
                                                <span class="Apple-converted-space">&amp;nbsp;</span>Seller represents, warrants,
                                                certifies and covenants (collectively “<b>Covenants</b>”) that it will comply with all
                                                laws applicable to the goods and/or the activities contemplated or provided
                                                under each Purchase Order, including, but not limited to, any national,
                                                international, federal, state, provincial or local law, treaty, convention,
                                                protocol, common law, regulation, directive or ordinance and all lawful orders,
                                                including judicial orders, rules and regulations issued thereunder, including
                                                without limitation those dealing with the health and safety, records retention
                                                and the transportation or storage of hazardous materials.  Seller shall also
                                                comply with good industry practices, including the exercise of that degree of skill,
                                                diligence, prudence and foresight which can reasonably be expected from a competent
                                                Seller of the goods. Seller further agrees at Buyer’s request to provide certificates
                                                relating to any applicable legal requirements or to update any and all of the certifications,
                                                representations and warranties under the Agreement in form and substance satisfactory to Buyer.
                                                With respect to all goods or other materials sold or otherwise transferred to Buyer hereunder,
                                                Seller shall provide all relevant information, including without limitation, material
                                                safety data sheets in the language and the legally required format of the location to
                                                which the goods will be shipped and mandated labeling information required pursuant to
                                                applicable requirements.
                                            </span>
                                        </li>
                                        <li class="li2">
                                            <strong>
                                                <span class="s3">DELIVERY AND PASSAGE OF TITLE.</span>
                                            </strong>
                                            <span class="s1">
                                                <!--<strong>.</strong> &amp;nbsp;-->
                                            </span>
                                            <ol class="ol2" style="list-style-type: lower-alpha;">
                                                <li class="li2">
                                                    <span class="s1">Time is of the essence of each Purchase Order.
                                                        Buyer shall be entitled to recover damages that it incurs as a
                                                        result of Seller’s failure to perform as scheduled.  Unless
                                                        expressly stated to the contrary, Buyer’s remedies are cumulative
                                                        and Buyer shall be entitled to pursue any and all remedies available
                                                        at law or equity.  If delivery of goods is not completed by the date
                                                        set forth in a Purchase Order, Buyer reserves the right, without liability
                                                        and in addition to its other rights and remedies at law, in equity or
                                                        under the terms of the Agreement and/or such Purchase Order, to purchase
                                                        elsewhere and hold Seller liable for any additional loss, cost, damage or
                                                        expense incurred thereby. Seller shall pay any loss, cost, damage or expense
                                                        resulting from the untimely receipt of the goods ordered. Seller shall notify
                                                        Buyer immediately if it is unable to ship timely. Buyer shall have the right
                                                        to refuse any goods with untimely delivery and to cancel the balance of a
                                                        Purchase Order for any part of the goods due after untimely delivery of any
                                                        installments. By accepting the untimely delivery of any installment, Buyer
                                                        shall not be bound to accept future shipments nor be deprived of its right
                                                        to return goods already accepted nor to claim damages for untimely delivery.
                                                        If Buyer accepts any advance shipment (other than requested by it) under any
                                                        Purchase Order, payment terms on such shipment shall be computed from the
                                                        required shipping date.
                                                    </span>
                                                </li>
                                                <li class="li2">
                                                    <span class="s1">(b)	Unless otherwise stated on the face of a
                                                        Purchase Order, goods shall be delivered FOB Buyer’s designated facility.
                                                    </span>
                                                </li>
                                            </ol>
                                        </li>
                                        <li class="li2">
                                            <strong>
                                                <span class="s3">ORDER POSTPONEMENT.</span>
                                            </strong>
                                            <span class="s1">
                                             <!--   <strong>.</strong> &amp;nbsp;-->
                                                <span class="Apple-converted-space">&amp;nbsp;</span>Buyer shall have the
                                                right to require Seller to postpone shipment of goods covered by one or
                                                more Purchase Orders, and Seller shall take all reasonable steps to
                                                minimize costs during such suspension.
                                            </span>
                                        </li>
                                        <li class="li2">
                                            <strong>
                                                <span class="s3">ORDER TERMINATION WITHOUT CAUSE.</span>
                                            </strong>
                                            <span class="s1">
                                             <!--   <strong>.</strong> &amp;nbsp;-->
                                                <span class="Apple-converted-space">&amp;nbsp;</span>In addition to Buyer’s
                                                right to terminate a Purchase Order for cause as provided below, Buyer
                                                may terminate the Agreement in whole or in part at any time upon notice
                                                to Seller.  Any termination by Buyer whether for cause or otherwise,
                                                shall be without prejudice to any claims for damages or other rights of
                                                Buyer against Seller, and Seller shall continue performance of any
                                                outstanding Purchase Order(s) to the extent not terminated.
                                            </span>
                                        </li>
                                        <li class="li2">
                                            <strong>
                                                <span class="s3">RIGHT OF INSPECTION.</span>
                                            </strong>
                                            <span class="s1">
                                                <!--<strong>.
                                                </strong> --><span class="Apple-converted-space"></span>
                                                Goods will be subject to Buyer’s inspection on arrival, notwithstanding
                                                prior payment to obtain discount. Defective goods will be returned at
                                                Seller’s expense and credit taken on settlements. Seller agrees to
                                                immediately replace defective goods so returned if the Buyer shall require,
                                                but the Buyer shall not be required to order or take replacements.
                                            </span>
                                        </li>
                                        <li class="li2">
                                            <strong>
                                                <span class="s3">RIGHT TO REFUSE GOODS.</span>
                                            </strong>
                                            <span class="s1">
                                                <!--<strong>.</strong>-->
                                                <span class="Apple-converted-space">&amp;nbsp;</span>
                                                Without limiting any other right of Buyer herein, Buyer shall have the
                                                right to reject and refuse goods that are not in strict accordance with
                                                the terms of a Purchase Order, the specifications or industry standard,
                                                or which are different in quality or quantity from that ordered, or which
                                                are shipped other than as specified under such Purchase Order or which are
                                                believed by Buyer to violate a third party's rights. Buyer may, at its sole
                                                discretion, either return rejected goods or hold the same at Seller’s risk
                                                and expense and may, in either event, charge the Seller with the cost of
                                                transportation, shipping, unpacking, examining, repacking, storing, reshipping
                                                and other like expenses.  If Seller fails to accept goods returned by Buyer,
                                                then Buyer shall have the right to dispose of such goods by any means.
                                                If within thirty (30) days after a request by Buyer for direction regarding
                                                disposition of rejected goods, Seller does not respond to Buyer, then Buyer
                                                shall have the right to dispose of the goods by any means. Acceptance of any
                                                prior shipments contrary to a Purchase Order shall not be considered a waiver
                                                of Buyer’s right to return any or all of the goods and receive full credit therefore.
                                                Authorization for substitution of style, color, size, quantity or other departure
                                                from the terms of a Purchase Order, is permitted only upon the written, signed and
                                                dated consent of Buyer.  Any claims made by Buyer for defective goods, shortages,
                                                returns, damages, or other claim of set off asserted as a result of Seller’s failure
                                                to comply with a Purchase Order will be charged back to Seller and the amount thereof
                                                deducted from payments to be made to Seller or, at Buyer’s option, will be promptly
                                                refunded to Buyer.
                                            </span>
                                        </li>
                                        <li class="li2">
                                            <strong>
                                                <span class="s3">RIGHT TO REJECT AND RETURN GOODS.</span>
                                            </strong>
                                            <span class="s1">
                                                <!--<strong>.</strong>-->
                                                <span class="Apple-converted-space">&amp;nbsp;</span>
                                                Without limiting any other right of Buyer herein, Buyer may at any time
                                                after delivery of the goods (and whether or not the same have been accepted
                                                by Buyer) reject and return all or part of the goods if any part is found
                                                to be in a damaged or defective condition or if believed by Buyer to violate
                                                a third party's rights. Seller shall refund to Buyer in full the price paid
                                                by Buyer for such returned goods. Any goods so returned shall be at Seller’s
                                                risk and expense, and Seller shall be responsible for all freight and handling charges.
                                            </span>
                                        </li>
                                        <li class="li2">
                                            <strong>
                                                <span class="s3">CONFIDENTIAL OR PROPRIETARY INFORMATION AND PUBLICITY.</span>
                                            </strong>
                                            <span class="s1">
                                                <!--<strong>.</strong>-->
                                                <span class="Apple-converted-space">&amp;nbsp;</span>
                                                Seller shall keep confidential any technical, process, proprietary or
                                                economic information, including the terms of the applicable Purchase Order,
                                                furnished by Buyer in connection with the Agreement (the “<b>Confidential
                                                Information</b>”) and shall not divulge, directly or indirectly, the Confidential
                                                Information for the benefit of any other party without Buyer's prior written
                                                consent.  Except as required for the efficient performance of a Purchase
                                                Order, Seller shall not use or permit copies to be made of the Confidential
                                                Information without Buyer’s prior written consent.  The restrictions in this
                                                Section regarding the Confidential Information shall be inoperative as to
                                                particular portions of the Confidential Information disclosed by Buyer to
                                                Seller if such information: (i) is or becomes generally available to the
                                                public other than as a result of disclosure by Seller; (ii) was available
                                                on a non-confidential basis prior to its disclosure to Seller; (iii) is or
                                                becomes available to Seller on a non-confidential basis from a source other
                                                than Buyer when such source is not, to the best of Seller’s knowledge, subject
                                                to a confidentiality obligation with Buyer, or (iv) was independently developed
                                                by Seller, without reference to the Confidential Information, and Seller can
                                                verify the development of such information by written documentation.  Upon
                                                completion or termination of a Purchase Order, Seller shall promptly return
                                                to Buyer all Confidential Information received in connection with such Purchase
                                                Order, including any copies thereof.  Any knowledge or information, which Seller
                                                shall have disclosed or may hereafter disclose to Buyer and which in any way relates
                                                to the goods purchased under a Purchase Order, or otherwise relates to the Agreement,
                                                shall not be deemed to be confidential or proprietary and shall be acquired by Buyer
                                                free from any restrictions (other than a claim for infringement) as part of the
                                                consideration for the Agreement and notwithstanding any copyright or other notice
                                                thereon, Buyer shall have the right to use, copy, modify and disclose the same as
                                                it sees fit.
                                            </span>
                                        </li>
                                        <li class="li2">
                                            <strong>
                                                <span class="s3">TERMINATION.</span>
                                            </strong>
                                            <span class="s1">
                                                <!--<strong>.</strong>-->
                                            </span>
                                            <ol class="ol2" style="list-style-type: lower-alpha;">
                                                <li class="li2">
                                                    <span class="s1">
                                                        <I>Termination for Default.</I>  Except for delay due to causes beyond
                                                        the control and without the fault or negligence of Seller (lasting
                                                        not more than 60 days), Buyer, without liability, may by written
                                                        notice of default, terminate the Agreement or the whole or any part
                                                        a Purchase Order:  (a) if Seller fails to perform within the time
                                                        specified in such Purchase Order or in any written extension granted
                                                        by Buyer; (b) if Buyer receives notice of an allegation of proprietary
                                                        rights infringement or believes that there may be an infringement of
                                                        proprietary rights regarding the goods that are the subject matter of
                                                        such Purchase Order; or (c) if Seller fails to comply with any of the
                                                        other terms of such Purchase Order.  Such termination shall become
                                                        effective if Seller does not cure such failure within ten (10) days
                                                        of receiving notice of default.  Seller shall continue performance
                                                        of any other outstanding Purchase Order to the extent not terminated
                                                        and shall be liable to Buyer for any excess costs for such similar
                                                        goods or services.  As an alternate remedy and in lieu of termination
                                                        for default, Buyer, at its sole discretion, may elect to extend the
                                                        delivery schedule and/or waive other deficiencies in Seller's
                                                        performance, making Seller liable for any costs, expenses or damages
                                                        arising from any failure of Seller’s performance.  If Seller for any
                                                        reason anticipates difficulty in complying with the required delivery
                                                        date, or in meeting any of the other requirements of a Purchase Order,
                                                        Seller shall promptly notify Buyer in writing.  If Seller does not
                                                        comply with Buyer's delivery schedule, Buyer may require delivery by
                                                        fastest method and charges resulting from the premium transportation
                                                        must be fully prepaid by Seller.  Buyer’s rights and remedies in this
                                                        clause are in addition to any other rights and remedies provided by law,
                                                        equity or under the Agreement.
                                                    </span>
                                                </li>
                                                <li class="li2">
                                                    <span class="s1">
                                                        <I>Termination for Insolvency/Prolonged Delay.</I>  If Seller ceases to
                                                        conduct its operations in the normal course of business or fails
                                                        to meet its obligations as they mature or if any proceeding under
                                                        the bankruptcy or insolvency laws is brought by or against Seller,
                                                        a receiver for Seller is appointed or applied for, an assignment
                                                        for the benefit of creditors is made or an excused delay (or the
                                                        aggregate time of multiple excused delays) lasts more than 60 days,
                                                        Buyer may immediately terminate this Agreement without liability,
                                                        except for goods delivered and accepted within a reasonable period
                                                        after termination (which will be paid for at the applicable Purchase
                                                        Order price).
                                                    </span>
                                                </li>
                                            </ol>
                                        </li>
                                        <li class="li2">
                                            <strong>
                                                <span class="s3">INDEMNITY.</span>
                                            </strong>
                                            <span class="s1">
                                                <!--<strong>.</strong>-->
                                                <span class="Apple-converted-space">&amp;nbsp;</span>
                                                Seller shall defend, indemnify, release and hold harmless Buyer, its
                                                directors, officers, employees, agents representatives, successors and
                                                assigns, whether acting in the course of their employment or otherwise,
                                                against any and all suits, actions, or proceedings, at law or in equity,
                                                and from any and all claims (including without limitation claims of
                                                negligent or willful misconduct or breaches of warranty), demands, losses,
                                                judgments, fines, penalties, damages, costs, expenses, or liabilities
                                                (including without limitation claims for personal injury or property or
                                                environmental damage, claims or damages payable to customers of Buyer)
                                                arising from any act or omission of Seller, its agents, employees, or
                                                subcontractors, except to the extent attributable to the sole and direct
                                                gross negligence of Buyer.  Seller further agrees to indemnify Buyer for
                                                any attorneys’ fees or other costs that Buyer incurs in the event that
                                                Buyer has to file a lawsuit to enforce any indemnity or additional insured
                                                provision of the Agreement.
                                            </span>
                                        </li>
                                        <li class="li2">
                                            <strong>
                                                <span class="s3">LIMITATION OF LIABILITY.</span>
                                            </strong>
                                            <span class="s1">
                                                <!--<strong>.</strong>-->
                                                <span class="Apple-converted-space">&amp;nbsp;</span>
                                                Buyer shall not be liable for any special, incidental, punitive or
                                                consequential damages arising out of or related to the Agreement,
                                                including any termination, rejection, or revocation of acceptance of all
                                                or any part of the applicable Purchase Order or any goods.  In no event
                                                shall Buyer’s liability hereunder exceed the purchase price of the
                                                applicable Purchase Order giving rise to the claim or action.
                                            </span>
                                        </li>
                                        <li class="li2">
                                            <strong>
                                                <span class="s3">GOVERNING LAW.</span>
                                            </strong>
                                            <span class="s1">
                                                <!--<strong>.</strong>-->
                                                <span class="Apple-converted-space">&amp;nbsp;</span>
                                                The Agreement (and each Purchase Order contained therein) shall in all
                                                respects be governed by and interpreted in accordance with the substantive
                                                law of the Commonwealth of Pennsylvania, excluding its conflicts of law provisions.
                                            </span>
                                        </li>
                                        <li class="li2">
                                            <strong>
                                                <span class="s3">DISPUTE RESOLUTION.</span>
                                            </strong>
                                            <span class="s1">
                                                <!--<strong>.</strong>-->
                                                <span class="Apple-converted-space">&amp;nbsp;</span>
                                                Except for claims seeking equitable relief, the parties shall attempt to
                                                amicably resolve any controversy, dispute or difference arising out of the
                                                Agreement and/or a Purchase Order.  Except for claims seeking equitable
                                                relief, any unresolved dispute shall be referred to a qualified independent
                                                arbitrator acceptable to both parties. Any arbitration under the Agreement
                                                shall take place in Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania. The arbitrator will have no
                                                authority to award any damages that are excluded by the terms of the Agreement.
                                                In the event that a suitable independent arbitrator cannot be identified and
                                                agreed on by both parties within twenty (20) days of the first demand by a
                                                party for arbitration, then the parties agree that a single arbitrator will
                                                be appointed by the American Arbitration Association (AAA). All arbitration
                                                proceedings shall be conducted in accordance with the Commercial Arbitration
                                                Rules of the AAA, but shall be administered by AAA only if AAA appoints the
                                                arbitrator. The arbitrator may award attorney’s fees and costs as part of the
                                                award. The award of the arbitrator shall be final and binding and may be
                                                entered as a judgment in any court of competent jurisdiction. All proceedings
                                                shall be conducted in the English language, unless otherwise stated in the
                                                applicable Purchase Order.  The award shall be final and binding on both Buyer
                                                and Seller, and the parties hereby waive the right of appeal to any court for
                                                amendment or modification of the arbitrator’s award.
                                            </span>
                                        </li>
                                        <li class="li2">
                                            <strong>
                                                <span class="s3">WAIVER.</span>
                                            </strong>
                                            <span class="s1">
                                                <!--<strong>.</strong>-->
                                                <span class="Apple-converted-space">&amp;nbsp;</span>
                                                No claim or right arising out of a breach of the Agreement or a Purchase
                                                Order can be discharged in whole or in part by a waiver or renunciation unless
                                                supported by consideration and made in writing signed by the aggrieved party.
                                                Either party’s failure to enforce any provisions hereof shall not be construed
                                                a waiver of a party’s right thereafter to enforce each and every such provision.
                                            </span>
                                        </li>
                                        <li class="li2">
                                            <strong>
                                                <span class="s3">ENTIRE AGREEMENT.</span>
                                            </strong>
                                            <span class="s1">
                                                <!--<strong>.</strong>-->
                                                <span class="Apple-converted-space">&amp;nbsp;</span>
                                                The Agreement, with documents as are expressly incorporated by reference,
                                                is intended as a complete, exclusive and final expression of the parties’
                                                agreement with respect to the subject matter herein and supersedes any prior
                                                or contemporaneous agreements, whether written or oral, between the parties.
                                                No course of prior dealings and no usage of the trade shall be relevant to
                                                determine the meaning of the Agreement even though the accepting or acquiescing
                                                party has knowledge of the performance and opportunity for objection.
                                                The term “<b>including</b>” shall mean and be construed as “<b>including, but not
                                                limited to</b>”, unless expressly stated to the contrary.  The invalidity, in
                                                whole or in part, of any of the foregoing articles or paragraphs of the
                                                Terms and Conditions shall not affect the remainder of such articles or
                                                paragraphs or any other article or paragraph of the Agreement, which
                                                shall continue in full force and effect.  Further, the parties agree to
                                                give any such article or provision deemed invalid, in whole or in part,
                                                a lawful interpretation that most closely reflects the original intention
                                                of Buyer and Seller.  All provisions or obligations contained in the Agreement,
                                                which by their nature or effect are required or intended to be observed,
                                                kept or performed after termination or expiration will survive and remain
                                                binding upon and for the benefit of the parties, their successors
                                                (including without limitation successors by merger) and permitted assigns.
                                            </span>
                                        </li>
                                    </ol>
                                </div>
                            </div>
                        </div>
                    </div>
                </section>
            </t>
        </t>
    </template>
</odoo>