<odoo>
    <template id="testimonials_page" name="Testimonials">
        <t t-name="website.testimonials">
            <t t-call="website.layout">
                <div id="wrap" class="oe_structure oe_empty">
                    <section class="s_title">
                        <div class="container">
                            <div class="row">
                                <div class="col-md-12">
                                    <h1 class="text-center">Testimonials</h1>
                                    <h3 class="text-center text-muted">TAKE THEIR WORD FOR IT. OUR CUSTOMERS SPEAK
                                        VOLUMES ABOUT OUR SERVICES, HERE’S WHAT THEY HAVE TO SAY:
                                    </h3>
                                </div>
                            </div>
                        </div>
                    </section>
                    <div id="myCarousel1567380584379" class="carousel slide s_banner s_carousel s_carousel_default"
                         data-interval="10000" style="">
                        <ol class="carousel-indicators">
                            <li data-target="#myCarousel1567380584379" data-slide-to="0" class="active"/>
                            <li data-target="#myCarousel1567380584379" data-slide-to="1"/>
                            <li data-target="#myCarousel1567380584379" data-slide-to="2"/>
                            <li data-target="#myCarousel1567380584379" data-slide-to="3"/>
                            <li data-target="#myCarousel1567380584379" data-slide-to="4"/>
                            <li data-target="#myCarousel1567380584379" data-slide-to="5"/>
                            <li data-target="#myCarousel1567380584379" data-slide-to="6"/>
                            <li data-target="#myCarousel1567380584379" data-slide-to="7"/>
                            <li data-target="#myCarousel1567380584379" data-slide-to="8"/>
                            <li data-target="#myCarousel1567380584379" data-slide-to="9"/>
                        </ol>
                        <div class="carousel-inner">
                            <div class="active carousel-item oe_custom_bg oe_img_bg">
                                <div class="container">
                                    <div class="row content">
                                        <div class="carousel-content col-md-12 mt128 mb96" style="">
                                            <h4>A career at SPS gave me the opportunity to progress not only
                                                professionally, but personally. The potential for growth here is
                                                uncapped, which allows us to set our goals high and reach them. We are
                                                immersed into such a motivating atmosphere that encourages us to
                                                constantly learn new things, and pushes us to exceed our own
                                                expectations.
                                            </h4>
                                            <p>- Brittany Edwards, Sales Account Manager, 13 months</p>
                                        </div>
                                    </div>
                                </div>
                            </div>
                            <div class="carousel-item oe_custom_bg oe_img_bg">
                                <div class="container">
                                    <div class="row content">
                                        <div class="carousel-content col-md-12 mt128 mb96" style="">
                                            <h4>I love working at SPS because of the opportunity for personal and
                                                professional growth. The work environment enhances the ability for both
                                                individual and team success. While the company’s culture provides
                                                opportunity for innovative career experiences.
                                            </h4>
                                            <p>- Matt Zardecki, Acquisition Manager, 3 years at SPS</p>
                                        </div>
                                    </div>
                                </div>
                            </div>
                            <div class="carousel-item oe_custom_bg oe_img_bg">
                                <div class="container">
                                    <div class="row content">
                                        <div class="carousel-content col-md-12 mt128 mb96" style="">
                                            <h4>One of the many reasons why I love SPS is the opportunity for growth and
                                                development. Working at SPS has allowed me to take my passion for
                                                medical device sales to the next level with the ongoing training and
                                                motivational coworkers it provides. The culture here makes it feel like
                                                a family, we all share the same core values and push each other to
                                                better ourselves every day. Its hands down one of the best places I have
                                                ever worked.
                                            </h4>
                                            <p>- Chelsea Cernigliaro, Sales Manager, 3 years at SPS</p>
                                        </div>
                                    </div>
                                </div>
                            </div>
                            <div class="carousel-item oe_custom_bg oe_img_bg">
                                <div class="container">
                                    <div class="row content">
                                        <div class="carousel-content col-md-12 mt128 mb96" style="">
                                            <h4>SPS is the type of place that you work if you want your personal and
                                                professional aspirations to go from dreams to reality. I work in a space
                                                that promotes growth and creativity—alongside leadership that is
                                                adaptive and responsive. I’ve been at SPS for about a year now, and I
                                                look forward to the future of my career here.
                                            </h4>
                                            <p>- Whitney Rathfon, Capital Equipment Manager</p>
                                        </div>
                                    </div>
                                </div>
                            </div>
                            <div class="carousel-item oe_custom_bg oe_img_bg">
                                <div class="container">
                                    <div class="row content">
                                        <div class="carousel-content col-md-12 mt128 mb96" style="">
                                            <h2 class="o_default_snippet_text">Your Slide Title</h2>
                                            <h4>[to Jenn] All I can say is that SPS, and especially you, are genuine,
                                                professional and extremely pleasant. You all will go above and beyond to
                                                help us out any way you can. It has been a true pleasure.
                                            </h4>
                                            <p>- Marty G., North Eastern Regional Hospital, RN, CNOR</p>
                                        </div>
                                    </div>
                                </div>
                            </div>
                            <div class="carousel-item oe_custom_bg oe_img_bg">
                                <div class="container">
                                    <div class="row content">
                                        <div class="carousel-content col-md-12 mt128 mb96" style="">
                                            <h4>We have worked with Surgical Product Solutions for the past year &amp;amp;
                                                a half. They have assisted us in purchasing our overstock items or items
                                                no longer being used at our facility. As many hospitals know, the
                                                original manufacturer is not always willing to "take back" product or
                                                provide "credit", so it is great to have a third party vendor like
                                                Surgical Product Solutions to help us out.
                                            </h4>
                                            <p>- Patty C., North Eastern Regional Hospital, Product Utilization/Resource
                                                Nurse
                                            </p>
                                        </div>
                                    </div>
                                </div>
                            </div>
                            <div class="carousel-item oe_custom_bg oe_img_bg">
                                <div class="container">
                                    <div class="row content">
                                        <div class="carousel-content col-md-12 mt128 mb96" style="">
                                            <h4>We have been nothing but pleased with the products and service we have
                                                received from Surgical Product Solutions. Customer service is prompt and
                                                friendly!
                                            </h4>
                                            <p>- Lisa W., A Great Lakes Surgery Center, OR Buyer</p>
                                        </div>
                                    </div>
                                </div>
                            </div>
                            <div class="carousel-item oe_custom_bg oe_img_bg">
                                <div class="container">
                                    <div class="row content">
                                        <div class="carousel-content col-md-12 mt128 mb96" style="">
                                            <h4>It is a pleasure working with Surgical Product Solutions. The
                                                cost-savings is amazing!! 10 times out of 10 we receive an immediate
                                                response to all of our Surgical needs.
                                            </h4>
                                            <p>- Kendra N., A South Central Region Surgery Center, Materials Manager</p>
                                        </div>
                                    </div>
                                </div>
                            </div>
                            <div class="carousel-item oe_custom_bg oe_img_bg">
                                <div class="container">
                                    <div class="row content">
                                        <div class="carousel-content col-md-12 mt128 mb96" style="">
                                            <h4>Since our hospital has partnered up with SPS, we have saved a tremendous
                                                amount of money! The customer service staff is always updating their
                                                catalog and sending it to me so that we can continue saving money.
                                                Thanks for all you do!
                                            </h4>
                                            <p>- Michelle W., A South Eastern Region Hospital, Inventory Control
                                                Specialist
                                            </p>
                                        </div>
                                    </div>
                                </div>
                            </div>
                            <div class="carousel-item oe_custom_bg oe_img_bg">
                                <div class="container">
                                    <div class="row content">
                                        <div class="carousel-content col-md-12 mt128 mb96" style="">
                                            <h4>SPS has allowed us to realize significant savings on our mesh needs,
                                                while maintaining compliance with our GPO contract. Thank you!
                                            </h4>
                                            <p>- Matthew J., North Eastern Regional Hospital, Director of Materials
                                                Management
                                            </p>
                                        </div>
                                    </div>
                                </div>
                            </div>
                        </div>
                        <div class="carousel-control-prev" data-label="Previous" data-slide="prev"
                             data-target="#myCarousel1567380584379" title="Previous" role="img">
                            <span class="carousel-control-prev-icon"/>
                            <span class="sr-only o_default_snippet_text">Previous</span>
                        </div>
                        <div class="carousel-control-next" data-label="Next" data-slide="next"
                             data-target="#myCarousel1567380584379" title="Next" role="img">
                            <span class="carousel-control-next-icon"/>
                            <span class="sr-only o_default_snippet_text">Next</span>
                        </div>
                    </div>
                </div>
            </t>
        </t>

    </template>
</odoo>